Good day!
طاب يومكم!
This is Quartz News Network at 6.
معكم Quartz News Network at 6.
I'm your host, Intelligent Seal.
مضيفكم, Intelligent Seal.
We would like to announce we've hired a whale to translate QNN into Arabic.
نعلن بكل سرور أننا وظفنا حوت لترجمة QNN إلى العربية. (انا <:)
It's incredible how well this whale can type on a human keyboard.
من المذهل مدى براعة هذا الحوت في الكتابة على لوحة مفاتيح بشرية.
Citizens from Dema have sent us letters declaring
أرسل لنا مواطنو ديما رسائل يعلنون فيها
people in the city are raising their levels of concern.
سكان المدينة يرفعون من مستويات القلق.
The authorities from Dema have told us to tell the citizens of Dema
طلبت منا سلطات ديما إبلاغ مواطني ديما
as well as you to report about what is bringing these levels of concern
وكذلك إبلاغكم بما يثير هذه المستويات من القلق.
to their minds, and the bishops will help you deal with it.
في أذهانهم، وسيساعدكم الكهنة على التعامل مع ذلك.
Other cities don't track their citizens’ levels of concern, but
المدن أخرى لا تتابع مستويات قلق مواطنيها، لكن
The Bishops have said that if you're feeling yours are higher than normal
قال الكهنة إنه إذا شعرت أن مستويات قلقك أعلى من المعتاد
you can feel free to contact them as well.
يمكنك التواصل معهم بحرية في أي وقت.
Breaking News
اخبار عاجلة.
We were just informed that Lupancham has stopped aiding
تم إبلاغنا للتو أن لوبانتشام توقفت عن تقديم الدعم
three Chunkian countries, including
ثلاث دول تشانكية، من بينها
RFM, Grapetopia and DRR.
RFM و Grapetopia و DRR.
This news came as a shock to residents of these Chunkian countries
جاء هذا الخبر صدمة لسكان هذه الدول التشانكية.
as they depended on Lupancham helping them with financial aid and
لأنهم اعتمدوا على لوبانتشام في مساعدتهم بالدعم المالي و
would not survive on their own.
ولن يستطيعوا البقاء على قيد الحياة بمفردهم.
We will also have our aids cut if we don't have this segway, to our sponsor
سوف تُقطع مساعداتنا أيضًا إذا لم نحصل على هذا التمويل، من راعينا
WELCOME TO FEDBANK
FEDBANK اهلآ الى
Have you ever thought that Minecraft didn't have enough banks?
هل فكرت يوماً ان ماين كرافت لا تحوي عدد مافٍ من البنوك؟
Well, we've got a solution for you!
لدينا الحل من اجلك!
Introducing FedBa- Ba- Ba- Ba- Ba-
نقدم فيدبا- با- با- با- با
Hello, Quartz News Network viewers
مرحباً, Quartz News Network مشاهدين
I'm Sauce Dude, vice president of The Strudel.
انا Sauce Dude, نائب رئيس Strudel.
Are you looking for a nice place to visit to escape the hell scape of panorama?
هل تبحث عن مكان جميل للهروب من جحيم بانوراما؟
If so, come stay at The Strudel for a bit!
اذاً، ابقى في سترودل لبعض الوقت!
for over half a year, the world of Strudel has been shaped by the democratic system and the players
لأكثر من نصف عام، شكّل نظام الديمقراطية وا للاعبون عالم سترودل.
so far, we've had 7 elections, 4 presidents, and 15 legislative meetings.
حتى الآن، أجرينا 7 انتخابات، وكان لدينا 4 رؤساء، و15 اجتماعًا تشريعيًا.
In our unique legislative system, every player is a member of the general assembly
في نظامنا التشريعي الفريد، كل لاعب هو عضو في الجمعية العامة.
every citizen of strudel votes on bills that can range from adding mods to the server, changing the rules, and deciding whether or not a player is gay
يصوّت كل مواطن في سترودل على مشاريع القوانين التي يمكن أن تتراوح بين إضافة تعديلات (مودات) إلى السيرفر، وتغيير القوانين، وتحديد ما إذا كان أحد اللاعبين مثليًا أم لا.
here in strudel, every player has the opportunity to write legislation, lead a party, or even run for president.
هنا في سترودل، لكل لاعب الفرصة لكتابة التشريعات، وقيادة حزب، بل وحتى الترشح لرئاسة الجمهورية.
Since December 22nd, players on craftocracy have been leaving their mark on the server history.
منذ 22 ديسمبر، كان اللاعبون في كرافتوقراطية يتركون بصمتهم في تاريخ السيرفر
Parties have succeeded, parties have failed, legislation has been passed, legislation has been blocked.
أحزاب نجحت، وأحزاب فشلت، تم تمرير تشريعات، وتم حظر تشريعات أخرى.
So come visit strudel, witness it all unfold live, and maybe become a citizen and member of the legislature.
فلتأتِ لزيارة سترودل، وكن شاهدًا على كل ما يحدث مباشرة، وربما تصبح مواطنًا وعضوًا في الهيئة التشريعية.
With our wide selection of mods, theres always something to do.
مع مجموعتنا الكبيرة من التعديلات (المودات)، هناك دائمًا شيء تفعله.
You could even try becoming the next big party leader or president, we're always looking for a shakeup!
يمكنك حتى محاولة أن تصبح زعيم الحزب الكبير القادم أو الرئيس، نحن دائمًا نبحث عن تغيير مثير!
We might even discover if you're gay or not!
قد نكتشف حتى ما إذا كنت مثليًا أم لا!
As you might've noticed, we're in a completely separate studio!
كما قد لاحظت، نحن في استوديو جديد تمامًا
This is Oak Studios, a Quartz Media studio in CRSS 3.
Oak Studios, CRSS 3 داخل Quartz Media ستيديو ل
We will be traveling back and forth to report news on both worlds!
سننتقل ذهابًا وإيابًا لتغطية الأخبار في كلا العالمين!
This specific episode doesn't have much special to report
لا يوجد في هذه الحلقة الكثير من الأخبار للتغطية.
so we're just going to show our studio and tell you stuff about the place.
لذا سنقوم فقط بعرض استوديوهاتنا ونخبركم ببعض المعلومات عن المكان.
Scientists have recently discovered that
اكتشف العلماء مؤخرًا أنَّ
the lesser known “Pooja Rocks” decay into “Amethyst” as time passes.
“Amethyst” الغير معروف يقوم بالتحلل ببطئ الى “Pooja Rocks”
We would like to show you samples, but unfortunately neither
نود أن نعرض لكم عينات، ولكن للأسف لا
Pooja Rocks nor Amethyst are on CRSS 3.
لا Pooja Rocks ولا Amethyst موجودان على CRSS 3
A few queer, creative, welcoming, and silly technologists
بعض التقنيين المثليين، المبدعين، المرحبين، والسخيفين.
from “Pridecraft Studios” have announced today they're
من “Pridecraft Studios” اعلنوا اليوم انهم
working on an instant-chat platform that utilizes the CRSS Internet to operate.
يعملون على منصة دردشة فورية تستخدم الإنترنت CRSS للتشغيل.
They've noted it will likely come out at the same time CRSSi is widely available.
لقد أشاروا إلى أنَّ المنصة من المحتمل أن تصدر في نفس الوقت الذي يصبح فيه CRSSi متاحًا على نطاق واسع.
That's it for today!
هذا كل شيءٍ لليوم!
Thanks for watching this edition of Quartz News Network and see you next month!
شكرًا لمشاهدتكم هذه الحلقة من Quartz News Network، ونراكم الشهر المقبل!